            filename: "patient_report_diabetes_PAT001.pdf",
            chunk_text: "Patient presents with Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus, well controlled on Metformin 1000mg twice daily. HbA1c levels have improved from 8.2% to 6.5% over the past 3 months. Patient demonstrates excellent medication adherence and lifestyle modification compliance.",
            content: "Patient presents with Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus, well controlled on Metformin 1000mg twice daily. HbA1c levels have improved from 8.2% to 6.5% over the past 3 months. Patient demonstrates excellent medication adherence and lifestyle modification compliance.",
            score: 0.94,
